Guide to the T. W. Anderson Papers SC0911
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-093
  - Subject Files
    - Karlin Volume Samuel Karlin: Reprints, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Karlin Volume Reception: Guest List, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Krieger Publishing Company, 1976-1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Lazarsfeld Volume Paper, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - London School of Economics (Sabbatical), 1973 Nov (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Longman Group Limited (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Los Angeles Police Department, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - MACSYMA - Instructions for using, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Markham Publishing Company (TSA), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Mathematica, Inc. 1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - McGraw-Hill Company, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company (TSA), 1961-1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - McGraw-Hill: Elementary Book, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Men of Achievement (International Biographical Centre) (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Men Women of Distinction (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Metron, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Multivariate Analysis Book, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Multivariate Analysis, Fifth International Symposium - University of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NAS Informal Ballot, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - NAS Ballot, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - NAS Star Ballot (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - NAS subgroup, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Natl' Acad. Meeting, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - NAS, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - NAS formal ballot, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - NAS, 1984 May (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - National Academy of Sciences Correspondence - Goddard, Dr. David R., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - National Academy of Sciences Meeting, 1977 Apr 24-27 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - National Academy of Sciences Panel of Reviewers, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - National Academy of Sciences Proceedings, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - NAS ballot, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - NAS Cramer (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - NAS Forms (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - NAS Sec 33, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - NAS foreign, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - NAS, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - NAS formal ballot, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - NAS Informal Ballot, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - NAS, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - NAS staff subgroup, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - NAS stat subgroup, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - NAS for assoc., 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - NAS, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - NAS sec 33, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - NAS nominations, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - NAS, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - National forensic center, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - National Research Council, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - National Research Council Assembly of Behavioral social sciences, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - National research council assembly of mathematical physical sciences, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - National Research Council - Canada, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - National research council committee on assessment of quality-related characteristics of research doctorate programs in the U.S., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - National research council committee on support of research in the mathematical sciences (COSRIMS), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - National Research Council commission on human resources, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Natural sciences and engineering research council- Canada, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - North-Holland publishing company, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - NSF correspondence, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - NSF: at Caltech, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - NSF correspondence Blackman, James H., 1969-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - NSF correspondence Bruce E. Trumbo, 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - NSF distribution lists for technical reports (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - NSF correspondence sponsored projects office, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - NSF evaluations, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - NSF grant - reports, annual (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - NSF grant- reports, final (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - NSF grant - request for funding increment, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - NSF grant - request for funding increment, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - NSF grant - requirements (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - NSF grant no. ses-7913976 final project report, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - NSF grant lists, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - NSF- economics program (P.C. Phillips), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - NSF proposal for grant, 1983-1986 Febr (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - NSF proposal, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - NSF proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - NSF proposal, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - NSF proposal, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - NSF proposal, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - NSF Research proposal evaluations, 1971-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - NSF proposal, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - NSF - Stanford procedural memoranda, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - NSF statistics program grants (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - NSF/NBER seminar on time series, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Nemmers (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Oberwolfach, 1981-1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Oceanroutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Oliver Boyd - contract (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Oliver Boyd - correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - ONR contract - copies, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - ONR contract - proposal for Research, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - ONR contract - proposals for extension, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - ONR contract - proposals for extension, 1969-1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - ONR contract - requirements, guidelines (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - ONR contract - report, final, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - ONR contract - reports, expense (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - ONR contract - reports, special, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - ONR Correspondence (DePriest, Douglas J.), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - ONR Correspondence (Lundegard, Robert J.), 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - ONR correspondence (McDonald, Bruce J.), 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - ONR correspondence (resident representative, ONR Stanford Sponsored Projects Office), 1973-1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - ONR correspondence (Wallenius, K. T. ), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - ONR correspondence (Wegman, Edward J.), 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - ONR: at Caltech, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - ONR Distribution List - unclassified technical reports, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - ONR meeting - Prague, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - ONR meeting - report on 1974 meeting of statistician in Prague (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - ONR Contract - reports, annual, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - ONR - Stanford Procedural Memoranda (payment of assistants, etc.), 1969-1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - ONR - technical memorandum, 1972 Feb (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - ONR - workshop, 1973 Jun (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1971-1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Payment records subscriptions, annual dues, book purchases, etc.), 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - personalities of America (American biographical institute) (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Personalities of the West and Midwest (American biographical institute) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Prentice-Hall, inc (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Prentice-Hall, inc. -A. H. Webster, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Presenting Statistical papers by Freeman, Gonzalez, Hoaglin, Kilss (Am. Statist., Vol. 37, 1983 May (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Preston publishing co., inc., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Psychometrika - refereeing, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - R.A. Fisher lecture and award (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Rand-MC Nally company (TSA) (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - refereeing, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - refereeing, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - refereeing, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - referee's reports, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - reprint requests, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - research information center, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Ronald press company (TSA), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Roy memorial volume, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Royal academy of sciences (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Royal Statistical Society, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1970-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sankhya (seeing Indian Statistical Institute) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - second international symposium on multivariate analysis, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Sigma Xi, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics (SIAM), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Stanford bookstore (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Stanford faculty club, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University AAUP - Stanford chapter, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University Academic Council, 1970-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University - Academic Senate, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Administrative Panel on Retirement, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Administrative Panel on Retirement, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Stanford University Annual Faculty Reports to the President, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University Bechtel International Center, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Stanford University Benefits and Records Office, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stanford University campus report, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Stanford University Committee on Computation Facilities, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Stanford University committee on undergraduate studies, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University CIT (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Stanford University committee on FAC/staff affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Stanford University committee on FAC/staff affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Stanford University committee on FAC/staff affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Stanford University committee on fac/staff affairs tuition benefit, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Stanford University - statistics stat 233 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Stretzle / Stanford, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Stanford University - honor code 273 exam, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Stanford University - controller's office, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Stanford University Dean of Humanities and Sciences, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Stanford University Economics Department, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics Faculty meetings (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Faculty selection committee, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics search committee, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics search committee, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics search committee, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Stanford University Department of Statistics search committee - candidates, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Stanford University - Honor code324B exam (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Stanford University - Hoover institution (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Stanford University Humanities sciences - office of the dean, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Stanford University housing office, Escondido Village, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Stanford University Land Use (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Stanford University Lots computer, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Stanford University Mathematics - computer sciences library (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Stanford University memos to principal investigators, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Stanford University parking, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Stanford University patent agreement, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Stanford University retirement plan alternatives, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Stanford University publications, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Stanford University SCIP (Stanford Center for Information Processing), 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Stanford- SRI Study Committee, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - SWOPSI, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Statistical Analysis of time series, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Technometrics, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The Free Press (Macmillan Pub. Co.), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Tieto, LTD. (also see Journal of Time Series Analysis), 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - TSA F NEWS (Time Series Analysis and Forecasting Newsletter), 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - U - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Wald Memorial Fund, 1951-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Who's Who in America, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Who's Who in American Education, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Who's Who in California, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Who's Who in Science Engineering (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Who's Who in Technology Today, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Who's Who in Technology, 1980-1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Who's Who in the United States, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Who's Who in the West, 1981-1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Who's Who in the World (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Wiley- Advertising: Statistical Analysis of Time Series, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - WILEY- Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Wiley correspondence - G. R. Brahms, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wiley Correspondence - Bean, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Wiley correspondence, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Wiley correspondence - Davenport, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Ford Wiley, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Ford, Donald WILEY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Donald Ford Re: Agreement, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Wiley-Fransen, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Wiley Correspondence- Hildebrand, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Wiley Correspondence - Kessler, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Wiley Correspondence-McConnin, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Wiley Correspondence - Neilly, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Wiley Correspondence- Ostedt, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Wiley - Rappole, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Wiley - Halsted (W. Sullivan), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Stolle Wiley, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Geoff. Water Wiley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - W. Bradford Wiley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Robert E. Waleon, Wiley, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Wiley-Multivariate, Second Edition (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Wiley Correspondence - Shube, 1972-1988 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Bea, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Shufe, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Wiley- TSA sales, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Wiley - Wilks book, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Wilks volume, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Wilks, S. S., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - XYZ - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence
    - A - Miscellaneous, 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Amemiya, Takeshi, 1973-1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Amamiya, Yassuo, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, Oliver, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, R. L., 1981-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Ahrabi, Fereydoon, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Arrow, Professor Kenneth Minor Exam for Starr, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - B - Bek - Miscellaneous, 1970-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Bel - Miscellaneous, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - BAI, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Barndorff-Nielson, Professor Ole, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Baron, Ken, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Basu, Anupam (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Bateman, Paul T., 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Becker, Hellmut, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Belson, Irving (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Birnbaum, Professor Allan, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Brener, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Bundgaard, Svend, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Burstein, Dr. Herman (approximating the lower binomial confidence limit), 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Burstein, Dr. Herman (determining the appropriate sample size for confidence limits for a Proportion), 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1970-1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Cacoullos, Theo, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Chakravorti, S. R., 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Chan, N. N., 1980-1990 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Chen, Louis Hsiao-yun, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Chernoff, Professor Herman, 1972-1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Gleser, Leon Jay, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Choi, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Cohen, Professor Arthur, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Consul, Professor P. C., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Cox, Professor D. R., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Curtis, Alea, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Cutler, Preston, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Dalenius, Tore, 1970-1986 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Das Gupta (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Das Gupta, Somesh, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Dhrymes, Phoebus, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Durbin, James, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Durling, Dr. Frederick C. (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Dzhaparidze, K., 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - E - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Edelman, Murray (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Engel, Eduardo, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Eicker, Professor Friedhelm, 1969-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhart, Dr. Churchill, 1971-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Fang: 65th Birthday (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fang: Fellow of IMS, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Fang, Kai-Tai, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ferber, Robert, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Fisher, Professor Franklin M., 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Fleiss, Dr. Joseph L., 1975-1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Franklin, Professor H. Bruce, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - F - Miscellaneous, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Stat El - Gomal, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Goldberger, Professor Arthur S., 1970-1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Goldstein letter, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Good, I. J. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Gordon, Lou (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Granger, Clive, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - G - Miscellaneous, 1972-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Ghurye, Professor S. G., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Giri, N. C., 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Greenberg, Max, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Grenander, Ulf, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Griliches, Zvi, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - H - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Halmos, P. R., 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Aaron Han, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Han, Chien-Pai, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Hannan, Edward J., 1974-1984 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Hannegan, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Henry, Neil, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Hickman, Bert G., 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Hinich, Melvin, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Hinkley, Professor David, 1970-1983 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Hiromatsu, Takeshi, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Hosoya, Yuzo, 1974-1989 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Hotelling, Professor Harold, 1975-1989 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - HSIAO, Cheng, 1981-1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - P miscellaneous, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Parzen, Emanuel, 1970-1988 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Payne, D. J., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Pearson, E. S. Biometrika Tbls., 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Pesotchinsky, Leon Vitae, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Pratt, John W. (JASA) approx. lower binomial confidence limit1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Press, James, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Pynnonen, Seppo, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Puri, Madan L., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - HSU, P. L. - obituary, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Huber, Peter J., 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hussain, Dr. Mohammed Y., 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hutten, Professor E. H, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Huzii, Professor Mituaki, 1977-1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - I - Miscellaneous, 1966-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Ibragimov, I., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Intriligator, Michael D., 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - James, Mr. Edward T. Editor of Dictionary of American Bibliography, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - J - Miscellaneous, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Jensen, Donald R. (prof.), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Jogdeo, Kumar, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Norman L., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Johnstone, COPSS, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Johnstone, ASA fellow, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Howard L., 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Joreskog, 1973-1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Jorgenson, Dr. Dale W., 1969-1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1980-1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Kadane, Joseph B., 1974-1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Kagan, A. M., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - K edem, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Keiding, Niels (Dr.), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Kendall, M. G., 1970-1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Khatri, C. G., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Kiefer, Jack, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Kim, Han Keyn, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Kmenta, Jan, 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Komura, Kenji, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Koopmans, L. H., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Krishnaiah, Paruchuri, 1974-1987 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Krishnaiah, Dr. Paruchuri R. Covariance Matrices with Linear Structure, 1969-1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Kromer, Dr. Ralph E., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Kruskal, William, 1971-1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Kunitomo, Naoto, 1973-1983 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Laake, Petter, 1978-1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Lauritzen, Steffen, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Joseph M. Lay, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Lazarsfeld, Paul, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Lazlo Vita, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Lehmann, E. L., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Lehmann Festschrift paper (with Mentz), 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Levene, Howard, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Leone, Fred C., 1974-1986 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Lindgren, Bernard W., 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Linnik, Ju. V., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Lord, Frederic M., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Lyman, Richard W., 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - MA, 1969-1982 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - M- Miscellaneous, 1969-1982 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Maasoumi, Esfandiar, 1977-1986 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Madansky, Al, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Marcus, Leslie F., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Mardia, K. V., 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Mariano, Roberto S., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Mariano, Robert, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Mariano-Sawa, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Massy, William F., 1973-1981 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Matthes, D. K. Bunke, H., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mc - Miscellaneous, 1974-1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - McCoy, Thomas O., 1970-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Raul Mentz correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)